<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Session Logs on The Great Basin</title>
    <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Session Logs on The Great Basin</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 03 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-03/</guid>
      <description>Went we last ventured to the Great Basin, the date was 6 Fireharvest 1763.
The week was moving slowly, with few events of note. On the 7th, the task force was delivered a message from Vessimur Yutros, a delegate from the Principality of Vi. He told you that all the members of the task force were expected to appear before the assembled Forum in two days time on the 9th. When the task force entered the forum chambers, the delegates were loudly arguing over the protests at the docks two times before and weather the docks should be opened again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 06 February 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-06/</guid>
      <description>During our last foray into the Great Basin, Dr. Luna was working late in the Library with the green sample from the blast in the Forum chamber. Frustrated by her lack of progress, Dr. Luna conducted increasingly risky experiments until she passed a large amount of electricity through the material, were it promptly exploded destroying the entire lab, blowing a hole in the exterior of the library and nearly kills her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 10 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-10/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin, the data was 20 Fireharvest 1763.
The members of the task force were investigating the destruction of a warehouse on the docks of Taerwyn. Talking to Nessa Preston, captain of the Trobreryn guard, she told you that the guard was investigating the Keburipemi Syndicate and the tip had been given by an undercover guard named Arwyn Treharne, who is now missing. She seemed concerned that the task force&amp;rsquo;s plan involved them buying drugs, but did let them leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 17 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-17/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
It 20 Fireharvest 1763 and the members of the Task Force had infiltrated a hideout of the Keburipemi Syndicate. Upon entering the armory, they realized that they were not alone: two other members of the syndicate were polishing weapons. The two groups exchanged a few awkward glances when a figure that you were sure wasn&amp;rsquo;t their before suddenly appeared. The mysterious figure told the other syndicate members something in Niven and they quickly left the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 20 February 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-20/</guid>
      <description>During our last venture to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
The task force entered the Temple of Kroina and quickly noticed that everybody was sleep. They found some moderate strength magical auras in the temple and were just starting to question Diana when Alisha emerged from one of the storage rooms. She explains that Diana is blind and hopes that she wasn&amp;rsquo;t causing any problems. The task force is very suspicions about the two women and Alisha explains that she runs an apothecary called &amp;ldquo;Alisha&amp;rsquo;s Herbal Remedies and Tattoo Parlor&amp;rdquo; and that she is hear to restock something called Trance Wine which is used by worshipers of Kroina to place themselves in a deep meditative state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 20 March 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-20/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin,
The illustrious members of the task force were engaged in a battle with odd creatures with hunched backs, backwards hooved feet, elongated snouts and protruding tusks in the storage room of the Temple of Kroina in Kerkrad. After a feisty battle which saw several sun beetles&amp;rsquo; glowing guts getting scattered over the room, the creatures were defeated and upon death, they transformed into the corpses of regular boars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 23 Januray 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-23/</guid>
      <description>The Founder&amp;rsquo;s Gala of 1763 was two nights away. This prestigious event is held once a year to commemorate the establishment of Kerkrad as a city and the formal movement of the seat of power of the Koncord of Kieros to the floating island of Xylte.
The members of the soon to be established task force were scattered about the city, some like Oisin were dreaded their duty to attend the gala while the general atmosphere of the city was that of celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 24 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-24/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
It was Fireharvest 22nd and the members of the task force were engaged in a operation with the Taerwyn city guard against the Keburipemi Syndicate after receiving some intelligence from an operative within the Syndicate, Niwa, as assassin looking to humiliate Vicious in front of the upper leadership of the syndicate. Aided by Nessa Preston, a battle mage and several city guards, a hard fought battle ensued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 27 March 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-27/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
The date was 5 Fireharvest 1763 and the task force was gearing up to execute the warrant they have against Alisha&amp;rsquo;s Herbal Remedies and Tattoo Parlor. Initially their was some doubts on the behalf of Oisin on weather the task force should even be involved with this operation, but Eaton seemed to want you there. Alisha and the staff are not happy to be raiding, at least that is how they view it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 30 January 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-30/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin, the members of the task force were trying to get their grips on the clues left at the scene of the explosion. During a trip to the library to get the materials needed for a conspiracy board, Oisin and Will encountered Julius Peperthorn, Oisin&amp;rsquo;s Antiquarian. He seemed to think that Oisin was lucky for not getting expelled from the library and did drop some information about the missing Sword of Divinity, which apparently has connections to holy fire and that several people have tried to steal it in the past but where disintegrated in a burst of holy flames.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
