<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Session Logs on The Great Basin</title>
    <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Session Logs on The Great Basin</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (2023-02-26)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/2023-02-26-session-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/2023-02-26-session-log/</guid>
      <description>Session Recap Editor&amp;#39;s Note: This session was short and full of diversions, mainly do to the DM recovering from surgery and not having time to prepare material, although several other players had minor aliments as well.
When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The Task Force had just returned to Kerkard from the Roksduens there they had defeated a solider of the Caerwent Empire and reclaimed some valuable adamantine arms and armor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (2023-02-19)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Session Recapitulation When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The Task Force and their allies had just defeated a figure in adamantine armor who was leading a raiding party through the Calchiroos Tribe of the Roksduens. After downing him, Wil, Breagan and Jusa stripped his sword, shield and armor while binding him.
As you rested in shifts, one guard was posted to watch both the prisoner and the vast dessert around you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (2023-02-12)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Session Recapitulation When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The Task Force had just teleported to the Roksduens, the eastern edge of the Basin and home of Redfern. Once you reached Tomo, the closest thing to a capital of the Roksduens, you sought out Hibiscian Saffren, the elder of the Tomo tribe.
Upon entering the town hall, which also serves a number of other purposes ranging from tavern, inn, courthouse and legislature, you were approached by a young man a who told Redfern to cover his face and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (2023-02-05)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-02-05/</guid>
      <description>Session Recapitulation When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The Task Force was recovering from slaying Keburipemi with Niwa in a syndicate safe-house in Daitoshi, the Niven capital. Niwa explained that her sources told her that the Daimyos of the Imperium where frustrated that they had not been able to find you all for questioning after a homicide was committed during the Lantern Festival. Despite this, one of their own and a representative to the Koncord, Daimyo Ikoma, claimed to have seen Adobaizā Aoi lead you into a conference room before dismissing her against her protests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (2023-01-29)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-01-29/</guid>
      <description>Session Recapitulation When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The task force and their allies had stormed a remote monastery in the Niven Imperium, set on the volcano containing Keburipemi, the Niven deity of smoke, greed and misdirection who also was running the largest crime syndicate in the Basin. Before you stood the three masked avatars of Keburipemi. They let you quote &amp;#34;deliberate&amp;#34; for some time before asking the strength of your resolve and if there was room to negotiate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (22 January 2023)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-01-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-01-22/</guid>
      <description>Session Recapitulation When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The members of the Task Force and their allies where in a dire situation. After breaking into a remote monastery in the Niven Imperium to slay Keburipemi, one of the Harbingers of The Shattering and the current leader of the largest crime syndicate in the Basin, you engaged the monks and sages on the first floor of the temple. In quick succession, Obsidian Flow and Firefall caused most of the task force to become bound, blind and burning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Basin Session (08 January 2023)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-01-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/great-basin-2023-01-08/</guid>
      <description>Session Recap When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
The members of the Task Force and their allies were in a dire situation. After reaching the monastery which Niwa lead you to, a lengthy discussion ensued about the best way to enter the temple. You were not keen about using the 15-foot tall double doors but did not see any auxiliary entrances. After extensive debate, it was decided that you would enter on the second floor of the pagoda, which appeared to be a barracks or communal sleeping quarters for the monks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log (2022-12-04)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Session Recap When we last ventured to the Great Basin,
It still the 10th of Shimmerfall. After successfully stealing the life-stealing katana, Raifusutīrā, and meeting Niwa she used a bottle filled with gray liquid to transport the Task Force and herself into a remote part of the Niven forest. When asked if you would like to rest, you decided to push forward.
Eventually the party encountered a large gate marking the treeline on a trek up a mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log (2022-11-13)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-11-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-11-13/</guid>
      <description>Session Recap When we last ventured to the Great Basin,
It was the 10th of Shimmerfall, 1763 and the annual Niven Lantern Festival, which the members of the task force had been invited to using Zorro&amp;#39;s connections to the Krig Marchi Elenek and subsequently her personal friendship with a forum delegate from the Imperium, Ikoma. After a conversation with the owner of the Midnight Lotus, Takayama, the party believed that Niwa wanted them steal Raifusutīrā, the life stealing katana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log (2022-11-06)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-11-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-11-06/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin,
It was the 5th of Shimmerfall, 1763 and the members of the task force had just had an emergency meeting with the Forum, which did not end well.
After a day of downtime, you started to look towards the next thing on your agenda, the Niven Lantern Festival as well as the creation of more magic items using the funds recovered from the bottom of the canal in Daquin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log (2022-10-30)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-10-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-10-30/</guid>
      <description>This post is back dated from 7 Nov 2022 since I apparently forgot to write it.
When we last ventured to the Great Basin,
It was the 4th of Shimmerfall 1763 and the Annual Symposium of Arcane Masters was taking place on Kerkard, an event that Oisin had been looking forward to for some time. He and Breagan went to the Symposium, hosting in the Library of the Muse and learned all sorts of new and interesting things about magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log (2022-10-23)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-10-23/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin…
It was the 33rd of Fireharvest and the members of the task force had captured Marius Kleinheisterkamp and a member of the Keburipemi Syndicate after successfully taking control of the shipment of Cylex and collecting 84,000 gold from the bottom of the channel. Through collective rationale, it was decided that it was too dangerous to take these prisoners back to Kerkrad since their members of their governments could influence or disrupt the interrogation process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log (2022-09-25)</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-09-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-09-25/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin:
It was the 32nd of Fireharvest. The members of the Task Force had gotten tickets to the Niven Lantern Festival through a at times tense conversation between Marchi Elenek. Having prepared the day before with the other members of the Task Force, Zorro decided to take a three step approach.
Ask nicely. Positive reward, reveal that the Task Force knows of a threat related to the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 2022-09-11</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-09-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-09-11/</guid>
      <description>I seemed to have not taken any notes on this session, so this is all coming from memory, please correct me if I&amp;#39;m wrong about any of this stuff.
When we last ventured to the Great Basin:
It was 22 Fireharvest 1763. After receiving payment for the raid on the Kerkrad after it seemed clear that your contact within the Syndicate was not going to delivery any more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 24 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-24/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
It was Fireharvest 22nd and the members of the task force were engaged in a operation with the Taerwyn city guard against the Keburipemi Syndicate after receiving some intelligence from an operative within the Syndicate, Niwa, as assassin looking to humiliate Vicious in front of the upper leadership of the syndicate. Aided by Nessa Preston, a battle mage and several city guards, a hard fought battle ensued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 17 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-17/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
It 20 Fireharvest 1763 and the members of the Task Force had infiltrated a hideout of the Keburipemi Syndicate. Upon entering the armory, they realized that they were not alone: two other members of the syndicate were polishing weapons. The two groups exchanged a few awkward glances when a figure that you were sure wasn&amp;rsquo;t their before suddenly appeared. The mysterious figure told the other syndicate members something in Niven and they quickly left the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 10 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-10/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin, the data was 20 Fireharvest 1763.
The members of the task force were investigating the destruction of a warehouse on the docks of Taerwyn. Talking to Nessa Preston, captain of the Trobreryn guard, she told you that the guard was investigating the Keburipemi Syndicate and the tip had been given by an undercover guard named Arwyn Treharne, who is now missing. She seemed concerned that the task force&amp;rsquo;s plan involved them buying drugs, but did let them leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 03 April 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-04-03/</guid>
      <description>Went we last ventured to the Great Basin, the date was 6 Fireharvest 1763.
The week was moving slowly, with few events of note. On the 7th, the task force was delivered a message from Vessimur Yutros, a delegate from the Principality of Vi. He told you that all the members of the task force were expected to appear before the assembled Forum in two days time on the 9th. When the task force entered the forum chambers, the delegates were loudly arguing over the protests at the docks two times before and weather the docks should be opened again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 27 March 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-27/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
The date was 5 Fireharvest 1763 and the task force was gearing up to execute the warrant they have against Alisha&amp;rsquo;s Herbal Remedies and Tattoo Parlor. Initially their was some doubts on the behalf of Oisin on weather the task force should even be involved with this operation, but Eaton seemed to want you there. Alisha and the staff are not happy to be raiding, at least that is how they view it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 20 March 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-03-20/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin,
The illustrious members of the task force were engaged in a battle with odd creatures with hunched backs, backwards hooved feet, elongated snouts and protruding tusks in the storage room of the Temple of Kroina in Kerkrad. After a feisty battle which saw several sun beetles&amp;rsquo; glowing guts getting scattered over the room, the creatures were defeated and upon death, they transformed into the corpses of regular boars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 20 February 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-20/</guid>
      <description>During our last venture to the Great Basin&amp;hellip;
The task force entered the Temple of Kroina and quickly noticed that everybody was sleep. They found some moderate strength magical auras in the temple and were just starting to question Diana when Alisha emerged from one of the storage rooms. She explains that Diana is blind and hopes that she wasn&amp;rsquo;t causing any problems. The task force is very suspicions about the two women and Alisha explains that she runs an apothecary called &amp;ldquo;Alisha&amp;rsquo;s Herbal Remedies and Tattoo Parlor&amp;rdquo; and that she is hear to restock something called Trance Wine which is used by worshipers of Kroina to place themselves in a deep meditative state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 06 February 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-02-06/</guid>
      <description>During our last foray into the Great Basin, Dr. Luna was working late in the Library with the green sample from the blast in the Forum chamber. Frustrated by her lack of progress, Dr. Luna conducted increasingly risky experiments until she passed a large amount of electricity through the material, were it promptly exploded destroying the entire lab, blowing a hole in the exterior of the library and nearly kills her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 30 January 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-30/</guid>
      <description>When we last ventured to the Great Basin, the members of the task force were trying to get their grips on the clues left at the scene of the explosion. During a trip to the library to get the materials needed for a conspiracy board, Oisin and Will encountered Julius Peperthorn, Oisin&amp;rsquo;s Antiquarian. He seemed to think that Oisin was lucky for not getting expelled from the library and did drop some information about the missing Sword of Divinity, which apparently has connections to holy fire and that several people have tried to steal it in the past but where disintegrated in a burst of holy flames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Log 23 Januray 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/Pathfinder-GB/session-recaps/session-log-2022-01-23/</guid>
      <description>The Founder&amp;rsquo;s Gala of 1763 was two nights away. This prestigious event is held once a year to commemorate the establishment of Kerkrad as a city and the formal movement of the seat of power of the Koncord of Kieros to the floating island of Xylte.
The members of the soon to be established task force were scattered about the city, some like Oisin were dreaded their duty to attend the gala while the general atmosphere of the city was that of celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
